edmundlohcoaching.com 2012-10-11

# IM Initiation - Privacy Policy

**_Privacy Policy_**

**IMInitiation.com** values and respects the privacy of its visitors and members. This policy, known as the Privacy Policy, details the type of information we collect from you, and what we do with that information.

**_Personal Information_**

**IMInitiation.com** collects your First Name, and E-mail address when you first sign up with the site. We might also in the near future ask for additional, optional information through our registration form, including but not limited to your mailing address.

**_Use of Information_**

**We respect your privacy** and will never rent, share, trade or sell your information. You may easily unsubscribe at any time.

Upon request, **IMInitiation.com** may disclose your contact information to customers of your website, government agencies, any trademark or copyright owner requiring to contact you in regards to transactions or content on your site.

Information submitted by you at the time of registration (including but not limited to your name and e-mail address) may be used but not limited to marketing and promotional purposes by **IMInitiation.com**.

This information may also be shared with other companies who offer a co-branded or rebranded versions of our site, who offer services in conjunction with **IMInitiation.com** , or who are business partners of **IMInitiation.com**. **IMInitiation.com** will not otherwise identify you personally to other companies, or to any advertisers. **IMInitiation.com** provides demographic information in aggregate form to advertisers on our site, without identifying any user personally. 

We may use information provided by you when you participate in contests or surveys on our site to send information about **IMInitiation.com** to you, or to give information to advertisers in aggregate form.

By using **IMInitiation.com** and disclosing information to us you expressly consent to the uses described in this Privacy Statement.
